<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<languages>

    <English>
        <string name="backstories_1">Morning in Bloomwood is my favorite time. I grew up here, and from my apartment’s window, I can hear everyone waking up around me. The neighborhood used to feel as alive as the people. In the summer, folks fixed their cars outside my building and played music until the street lamps came on. There was always an end of summer block party, and always something to do. Now? Not so much.</string>
        <string name="backstories_2">Times have changed. People feel distant from each other. Developers built mixed use high rises, and new programs have come in bringing grants, funding, and new facilities. This was great, except the rents got higher and it felt like half the neighborhood was getting left behind. More and more of our old neighbors are moving out. More and more new faces are moving in, who aren’t as connected to the people already living here.</string>
        <string name="backstories_3">Not everyone in Bloomwood is getting a fair shake these days. Instead of talking to your neighbor, folks called in noise complaints. It feels like no one knows their neighbors anymore. We just keep to ourselves. I want to change that. Bloomwood was never the place where you ignored your neighbors. So I came up with a plan. A good one. As the Bloomwood Community Liaison to the city, I was able to secure a permit for an old school style block party to celebrate the reopening of our Community Center....</string>
        <string name="backstories_4">... I got us a bouncy house, food, even a health fair! Now I just have to convince some folks to help me work it. I know who to ask. I know how to ask them. I’ve always been good at connecting people and helping everyone out. Maybe if I can connect everyone in the neighborhood, Bloomwood can see that what really makes a neighborhood is not the buildings, or the grants, or the businesses that rush in. It’s the people.</string>
        
        <string name="ending_1">I’ve been talking so much about Bloomwood Spirit and getting this block party ready.  Today as we blocked off streets and inflated the giant bounce house, I wondered if all my efforts to help did the job. People have bigger issues. Health, money, family, school...did we make enough time? Share enough resources?</string>
        <string name="ending_2">Our Block Party is a connection between the old Bloomwood and the new Bloomwood. The smells of food and the whirring of the cotton candy machine all brought back memories. But could this bring the people?</string>
        <string name="ending_3">Just as I began to worry, Mr. Calindas arrived to set up the Healthcare tent. He patted me on the back before he went to instruct volunteer nurses on how to work with the community. “Paz and Jessica are showing up soon! Don’t worry!”</string>
        <string name="ending_4">I still worried, but it wasn’t long before Lila waved to me as she and Trisha carried art supplies, mobbed by several children who were as excited to see her outside of class as they were to see her in class. “Yes, I bought the facepaint and temporary tattoos! You just have to let me set up!”</string>
        <string name="ending_5">Rashad parked the library van, and Octavia and Charles sprinted towards the cotton candy machine. “Ya’ll don’t eat too much of that,” he called out, knowing full well they would eat too much of it.</string>
        <string name="ending_6">The trickle of people became a warm inviting crowd of neighbors. Mrs. Lee, all smiles, brought her grandson Eddie, who I haven’t seen in forever. “Do you remember my grandson, Eddie? I’m very proud of him.” Eddie looked just as proud of her.</string>
        <string name="ending_7">Elisa and her family carried succulents, and a few of her friends from school had boxes filled with extras. “We have the perlite, and the rocks. Mini Bloomwood terrariums, these are gonna be so cute!”</string>
        <string name="ending_8">We spent the whole day laughing, playing, and celebrating. Mr. Calindas was right. I didn’t need to worry. As music filled the neighborhood and the bounce house shook, I looked at my neighbors. We needed this. I needed this. We could be here, because we all helped each other. Bloomwood spirit has never been about the buildings, or the grants, or the businesses that rush in.</string>
        <string name="ending_9">It’s always been the people.</string>
        
        <string name="journal_updated">MyJournal Updated</string>
        <string name="todo_updated">MyTodo Updated</string>
        <string name ="phone_settings_app">Settings</string>
        <string name ="phone_contacts_app">Contacts</string>
        <string name ="phone_todo_app">To-do List</string>
        <string name ="phone_notes_app">My Journal</string>
    
        <string name="day">DAY</string>
        <string name="continue">CONTINUE</string>
        <string name="new_game">NEW GAME</string>
        <string name="tutorial">TUTORIAL</string>
        <string name="skip">SKIP STORY</string>
        <string name="next">NEXT</string>
        <string name="back">BACK</string>
        <string name="info">INFO</string>
        <string name="go_to_sleep">GO TO SLEEP</string>
        <string name="english">English</string>
        <string name="spanish">Spanish</string>
        
        <string name="pc_setup_title">Who are you?</string>
        <string name="name_field">Name</string>
        <string name="pronouns_field">Pronouns</string>
        <string name="language_field">Language</string>
        <string name="she_her">She/Her</string>
        <string name="he_his">He/His</string>
        <string name="they_them">They/Them</string>
        <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
        <string name="choose_one">Choose One</string>
        
        <string name="home">Home</string>
        <string name="community_center">Bloomwood Community Center</string>
        <string name="health_clinic">Bloomwood Health Clinic</string>
        <string name="library">Bloomwood Library</string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_1_title">A Little Help from Your Friends</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_1_desc">You found a library assistant in the YA section! Check in with Rashad and see how he’s doing.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_2_title">Under Pressure</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_2_desc">You helped Rashad learn about race based stress! Check in later and see how he’s doing.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_3_title">Running on Empty</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_3_desc">You helped Rashad figure out the next steps for getting therapy. Check in later to see how he’s feeling.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_4_title">A New Horizon</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_4_desc">You helped Rashad figure out the benefits of intergenerational outreach. Great work this week!</string>
    
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_1_title">LGBTQ+ Support</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_1_desc">You helped Lila with logistics for her first community event! Check in and see if she needs anything.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_2_title">Making time for what's important</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_2_desc">You helped Lila learn about her family health history options! See how she’s doing.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_3_title">Is this normal?</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_3_desc">You helped Lila get information and support for her feminine health care needs. Check in and see how she feels!</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_4_title">Where are my people?</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_4_desc">You helped Lila make new connections in the neighborhood! Great work this week!</string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_1_title">What the Community Really Needs</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_1_desc">Mr. Calindas feels like he’s prepared for the Health Fair! Check in later to see if he needs anything else.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_2_title">Mother Calindas' New Home</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_2_desc">Mr. Calindas feels like his Mother will love the neighborhood! Check in and see how he’s doing!</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_3_title">Tech Support for Mom</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_3_desc">You helped Mr. Calindas find some program options for Mother Calindas. Check in to see if he needs anything else!</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_4_title">Fun Day for Brooklyn</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_4_desc">Mr. Calindas’ family feels like the Block Party is going to be accessible for his granddaughter! Great work this week!</string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_1_title">Help Mrs. Lee verify that Eddie’s medication is correct</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_1_desc">You helped Mrs. Lee figure out the correct prescription for her grandson, Eddie. Check in with her, and see how she’s doing.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_2_title">Empower Mrs. Lee to schedule a doctor’s appointment</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_2_desc">You encouraged Mrs. Lee to seek treatment for her headaches! Check in on her and see if she needs anything else.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_3_title">Help Mrs. Lee prepare for her doctor's appointment</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_3_desc">Mrs. Lee is prepared for her doctor’s appointment! You should check in with her to see how she’s doing.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_4_title">Encourage Mrs. Lee to continue her health journey</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_4_desc">Mrs. Lee is feeling in charge of her health! Great work this week!</string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_1_title">Find out more info on career fairs</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_1_desc">You helped Elisa get ready for her career fair and learn networking tips. Check in with her and see how she is.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_2_title">Find out how to get vaccination records</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_2_desc">You helped Elisa with her immunization questions! Stop by and ask if she needs anything.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_3_title">Find a mentor for Elisa</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_3_desc">You helped Elisa get support as a first generation college student. Check in and see how she’s feeling.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_4_title">Find out more info on diabetes</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_4_desc">You helped Elisa and her Mom with diabetes information. Great work this week!</string>
        
        <string name="tutorial_building">Click on a building to see who’s at this location!</string>
        <string name="tutorial_phone">I use my phone to keep track of all the things I need to remember as a Community Liaison, and a good neighbor.</string>
        <string name="tutorial_todo">When I have something I need to do, it’s written in my To Do App. I like to keep track of any new information I have that can help other people in the neighborhood out.</string>
        <string name="tutorial_notes">I like to keep track of any new information I have that can help other people in the neighborhood out. I keep this in my Notes app.</string>
        <string name="tutorial_contacts">I like to help make connections in the community, so I make sure to keep my Contacts app updated to keep up with the lives and needs of my friends.</string>

    </English>

    <Spanish>

        <string name="backstories_1"></string>
        <string name="backstories_2"></string>
        <string name="backstories_3"></string>
        <string name="backstories_4"></string>

        <string name="ending_1"></string>
        <string name="ending_2"></string>
        <string name="ending_3"></string>
        <string name="ending_4"></string>
        <string name="ending_5"></string>
        <string name="ending_6"></string>
        <string name="ending_7"></string>
        <string name="ending_8"></string>
        <string name="ending_9"></string>

        <string name="journal_updated"></string>
        <string name="todo_updated"></string>

        <string name="day"></string>
        <string name="continue"></string>
        <string name="new_game"></string>
        <string name="tutorial"></string>
        <string name="skip"></string>
        <string name="next"></string>
        <string name="back"></string>
        <string name="info"></string>
        <string name="go_to_sleep"></string>
        <string name="english"></string>
        <string name="french"></string>

        <string name="pc_setup_title"></string>
        <string name="name_field"></string>
        <string name="pronouns_field"></string>
        <string name="language_field"></string>
        <string name="she_her"></string>
        <string name="he_his"></string>
        <string name="they_them"></string>
        <string name="first_name"></string>
        <string name="choose_one"></string>

        <string name="home"></string>
        <string name="community_center"></string>
        <string name="health_clinic"></string>
        <string name="library"></string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_1_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_1_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_2_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_2_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_3_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_3_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_4_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_4_desc"></string>
    
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_1_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_1_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_2_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_2_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_3_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_3_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_4_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_4_desc"></string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_1_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_1_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_2_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_2_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_3_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_3_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_4_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_4_desc"></string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_1_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_1_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_2_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_2_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_3_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_3_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_4_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_4_desc"></string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_1_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_1_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_2_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_2_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_3_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_3_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_4_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_4_desc"></string>

        <string name="tutorial_building"></string>
        <string name="tutorial_phone"></string>
        <string name="tutorial_todo"></string>
        <string name="tutorial_notes"></string>
        <string name="tutorial_contacts"></string>

    </Spanish>

</languages>