<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<languages>

    <English>

        <string name="backstories_1">Example 1</string>
        <string name="backstories_2">Example 2</string>
        <string name="backstories_3">Example 3</string>
        <string name="backstories_4">Example 4</string>

        <string name="ending_1">I’ve been talking so much about Bloomwood Spirit and getting this block party ready.  Today as we blocked off streets and inflated the giant bounce house, I wondered if all my efforts to help did the job. People have bigger issues. Health, money, family, school...did we make enough time? Share enough resources?</string>
        <string name="ending_2">Our Block Party is a connection between the old Bloomwood and the new Bloomwood. The smells of food and the whirring of the cotton candy machine all brought back memories. But could this bring the people?</string>
        <string name="ending_3">Just as I began to worry, Mr. Calindas arrived to set up the Healthcare tent. He patted me on the back before he went to instruct volunteer nurses on how to work with the community. “Paz and Jessica are showing up soon! Don’t worry!”</string>
        <string name="ending_4">I still worried, but it wasn’t long before Lila waved to me as she and Trisha carried art supplies, mobbed by several children who were as excited to see her outside of class as they were to see her in class. “Yes, I bought the facepaint and temporary tattoos! You just have to let me set up!”</string>
        <string name="ending_5">Rashad parked the library van, and Octavia and Charles sprinted towards the cotton candy machine. “Ya’ll don’t eat too much of that,” he called out, knowing full well they would eat too much of it.</string>
        <string name="ending_6">The trickle of people became a warm inviting crowd of neighbors. Mrs. Lee, all smiles, brought her grandson Eddie, who I haven’t seen in forever. “Do you remember my grandson, Eddie? I’m very proud of him.” Eddie looked just as proud of her.</string>
        <string name="ending_7">Elisa and her family carried succulents, and a few of her friends from school had boxes filled with extras. “We have the perlite, and the rocks. Mini Bloomwood terrariums, these are gonna be so cute!”</string>
        <string name="ending_8">We spent the whole day laughing, playing, and celebrating. Mr. Calindas was right. I didn’t need to worry. As music filled the neighborhood and the bounce house shook, I looked at my neighbors. We needed this. I needed this. We could be here, because we all helped each other. Bloomwood spirit has never been about the buildings, or the grants, or the businesses that rush in.</string>
        <string name="ending_9">It’s always been the people.</string>
        
        <string name="journal_updated">MyJournal Updated</string>
        <string name="todo_updated">MyTodo Updated</string>
        <string name ="phone_settings_app">Settings</string>
        <string name ="phone_contacts_app">Contacts</string>
        <string name ="phone_todo_app">To-do List</string>
        <string name ="phone_notes_app">My Journal</string>
        <string name ="phone_dictionary_app">Dictionary</string>
    
        <string name="day">DAY</string>
        <string name="week">Week</string>
        <string name="monday">Monday</string>
        <string name="tuesday">Tuesday</string>
        <string name="wednesday">Wednesday</string>
        <string name="thursday">Thursday</string>
        <string name="friday">Friday</string>
        <string name="saturday">Saturday</string>
        <string name="sunday">Sunday</string>

        <string name="monday_short">MON</string>
        <string name="tuesday_short">TUE</string>
        <string name="wednesday_short">WED</string>
        <string name="thursday_short">THU</string>
        <string name="friday_short">FRI</string>
        <string name="saturday_short">SAT</string>
        <string name="sunday_short">SUN</string>

        <string name="comm_manager">Community Manager</string>
        <string name="day_summary">Day Summary</string>
        <string name="continue">CONTINUE</string>
        <string name="new_game">NEW GAME</string>
        <string name="tutorial">TUTORIAL</string>
        <string name="skip">SKIP STORY</string>
        <string name="next">NEXT</string>
        <string name="back">BACK</string>
        <string name="exit_game">EXIT GAME</string>
        <string name="info">INFO</string>
        <string name="save">SAVE</string>
        <string name="go_to_sleep">GO TO SLEEP</string>
        <string name="current_task">Current Task</string>
        <string name="meet">Meet</string>
        <string name="good_morning_message">Good morning! Another beautiful week at Bloomwood. Ready to plan for a new Block Party?</string>
        <string name="completed">Completed</string>
        
        <string name="saved_games">Saved Games</string>
        <string name="next_npc">Who would be the next Block Party protagonist?</string>

        <string name="rashad_name">Rashad Williams</string>
        <string name="rashad_age_pronouns">42 years old | He/Him/His</string>
        <string name="rashad_title">Head Librarian, Bloomwood Library</string>
        <string name="rashad_description">Rashad Williams was born and raised in Bloomwood, and moved back after getting his Master’s Degree in Library Science. He is married with 2 children (Wife Cheryl, children Octavia and Charles) and started out as the popular Young Adult Librarian for Bloomwood Library. Since being promoted to Head Librarian last year, he’s tried to make new programs available for the Bloomwood Community. He enjoys comic books, science fiction, and is an avid runner.</string>
        <string name="lila_name">Lila Morgan</string>
        <string name="lila_age_pronouns">26 years old | She/Her/Hers</string>
        <string name="lila_title">Head Start Teacher, Community Center</string>
        <string name="lila_description">Lila Morgan grew up near Bloomwood, and moved to town when she was 17, where she worked with her mom at the Community Center, assisting her in her job as a Head Start teacher. After attending college at a state school nearby, Lila has recently returned to Bloomwood to take her mom’s position as she leaves to travel, and now lives in town with her partner Trisha. She is close with Mrs. Lee, and loves designing tattoos, teaching her border collie Charlie partner tricks, and long car rides with Trisha.</string>
        <string name="elisa_name">Elisa Ramirez</string>
        <string name="elisa_age_pronouns">19 years old | She/Her/Hers</string>
        <string name="elisa_title">College Student, Bloomwood Library</string>
        <string name="elisa_description">Elisa Ramirez grew up in Bloomwood, where her parents moved after leaving El Salvador. She’s currently living with her family while attending Bloomwood College. She loves reading, spending time with friends, physical activity, and the outdoors. She is currently the VP of her school’s nature club, and an aspiring freeclimber. She’s almost done with her Associates degree at Bloomwood College, and is currently getting ready to complete her Bachelor’s at a university nearby. She’s studying business, and intends to become a financial advisor once she graduates.</string>
        <string name="mrcalindas_name">Mr. Calindas</string>
        <string name="mrcalindas_age_pronouns">58 years old | He/Him/His</string>
        <string name="mrcalindas_title">Head Nurse, Bloomwood Health Clinic</string>
        <string name="mrcalindas_description">Giancarlo Calindas, is respectfully known as Mr. Calindas in the neighborhood. He moved into the neighborhood 20 years ago, when his wife, Paz took a job teaching Biology at Bloomwood Highschool. A second generation Filipino American, Mr. Calindas’ parents were farmworkers in Southern California, who brought him up with a strong sense of community. Mr. Calindas is the steward for his nurse’s union and likes to unwind by running. He cares deeply about the health and well-being of the neighborhood, and his daughter Jessica and his granddaughter, Brooklyn. </string>
        <string name="mrslee_name">Mrs. Lee</string>
        <string name="mrslee_age_pronouns">65 years old | She/Her/Hers</string>
        <string name="mrslee_title">Elder, Community Center</string>
        <string name="mrslee_description">Mrs. Lee is an elder in Bloomwood where she has lived for the last 20 years. Mrs. Lee and her husband Dr. Lee emigrated from South Korea with their grandson Eddie. Together, they raised Eddie in Bloomwood, speaking a mix of English and Korean. After the recent passing of her husband, Mrs. Lee schedules regular video calls with her Korean friends and occasionally with Eddie, when he’s not in his university library. Mrs. Lee loves attending fitness classes at the Community Center and her favorite color is pink!</string>

        <string name="days_left">DAYS LEFT</string>
        <string name="to_block_party">to block party for</string>
        <string name="please_note">Please Note!</string>
        <string name="progress_wont_save">Unfortunately, your progress made in the current task will not be saved.</string>
        
        <string name="english">English</string>
        <string name="spanish">Spanish</string>

        <string name="pc_setup_title">Who are you?</string>
        <string name="name_field">Name</string>
        <string name="pronouns_field">Pronouns</string>
        <string name="language_field">Language</string>
        <string name="she_her">She/Her</string>
        <string name="he_his">He/His</string>
        <string name="they_them">They/Them</string>
        <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
        <string name="choose_one">Choose One</string>
        <string name="welcome_title">Welcome to Bloomwood</string>
        <string name="welcome_text">Congratulations on your new role as the new Community Manager!</string>
        <string name="name_taken">Name is taken</string>

        <string name="home">Home</string>
        <string name="community_center">Bloomwood Community Center</string>
        <string name="health_clinic">Bloomwood Health Clinic</string>
        <string name="library">Bloomwood Library</string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_1_title">A Little Help from Your Friends</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_1_desc">You found a library assistant in the YA section! Check in with Rashad and see how he’s doing.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_2_title">Under Pressure</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_2_desc">You helped Rashad learn about race based stress! Check in later and see how he’s doing.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_3_title">Running on Empty</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_3_desc">You helped Rashad figure out the next steps for getting therapy. Check in later to see how he’s feeling.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_4_title">A New Horizon</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_4_desc">You helped Rashad figure out the benefits of intergenerational outreach. Great work this week!</string>
    
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_1_title">LGBTQ+ Support</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_1_desc">You helped Lila with logistics for her first community event! Check in and see if she needs anything.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_2_title">Making time for what's important</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_2_desc">You helped Lila learn about her family health history options! See how she’s doing.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_3_title">Is this normal?</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_3_desc">You helped Lila get information and support for her feminine health care needs. Check in and see how she feels!</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_4_title">Where are my people?</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_4_desc">You helped Lila make new connections in the neighborhood! Great work this week!</string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_1_title">What the Community Really Needs</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_1_desc">Mr. Calindas feels like he’s prepared for the Health Fair! Check in later to see if he needs anything else.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_2_title">Mother Calindas' New Home</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_2_desc">Mr. Calindas feels like his Mother will love the neighborhood! Check in and see how he’s doing!</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_3_title">Tech Support for Mom</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_3_desc">You helped Mr. Calindas find some program options for Mother Calindas. Check in to see if he needs anything else!</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_4_title">Fun Day for Brooklyn</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_4_desc">Mr. Calindas’ family feels like the Block Party is going to be accessible for his granddaughter! Great work this week!</string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_1_title">Help Mrs. Lee verify that Eddie’s medication is correct</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_1_desc">You helped Mrs. Lee figure out the correct prescription for her grandson, Eddie. Check in with her, and see how she’s doing.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_2_title">Empower Mrs. Lee to schedule a doctor’s appointment</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_2_desc">You encouraged Mrs. Lee to seek treatment for her headaches! Check in on her and see if she needs anything else.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_3_title">Help Mrs. Lee prepare for her doctor's appointment</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_3_desc">Mrs. Lee is prepared for her doctor’s appointment! You should check in with her to see how she’s doing.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_4_title">Encourage Mrs. Lee to continue her health journey</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_4_desc">Mrs. Lee is feeling in charge of her health! Great work this week!</string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_1_title">Find out more info on career fairs</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_1_desc">You helped Elisa get ready for her career fair and learn networking tips. Check in with her and see how she is.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_2_title">Find out how to get vaccination records</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_2_desc">You helped Elisa with her immunization questions! Stop by and ask if she needs anything.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_3_title">Find a mentor for Elisa</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_3_desc">You helped Elisa get support as a first generation college student. Check in and see how she’s feeling.</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_4_title">Find out more info on diabetes</string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_4_desc">You helped Elisa and her Mom with diabetes information. Great work this week!</string>
        
        <string name="tutorial_building">Click on a building to see who’s at this location!</string>
        <string name="tutorial_phone">I use my phone to keep track of all the things I need to remember as a Community Liaison, and a good neighbor.</string>
        <string name="tutorial_todo">When I have something I need to do, it’s written in my To Do App. I like to keep track of any new information I have that can help other people in the neighborhood out.</string>
        <string name="tutorial_notes">I like to keep track of any new information I have that can help other people in the neighborhood out. I keep this in my Notes app.</string>
        <string name="tutorial_contacts">I like to help make connections in the community, so I make sure to keep my Contacts app updated to keep up with the lives and needs of my friends.</string>
    </English>

    <Spanish>
        <string name="ending_1"></string>
        <string name="ending_2"></string>
        <string name="ending_3"></string>
        <string name="ending_4"></string>
        <string name="ending_5"></string>
        <string name="ending_6"></string>
        <string name="ending_7"></string>
        <string name="ending_8"></string>
        <string name="ending_9"></string>

        <string name="journal_updated"></string>
        <string name="todo_updated"></string>
        <string name ="phone_settings_app"></string>
        <string name ="phone_contacts_app"></string>
        <string name ="phone_todo_app"></string>
        <string name ="phone_notes_app"></string>

        <string name="day"></string>
        <string name="week"></string>
        <string name="monday"></string>
        <string name="tuesday"></string>
        <string name="wednesday"></string>
        <string name="thursday"></string>
        <string name="friday"></string>
        <string name="saturday"></string>
        <string name="sunday"></string>
        <string name="comm_manager"></string>
        <string name="day_summary"></string>
        <string name="continue"></string>
        <string name="new_game"></string>
        <string name="tutorial"></string>
        <string name="skip"></string>
        <string name="next"></string>
        <string name="back"></string>
        <string name="info"></string>
        <string name="save"></string>
        <string name="go_to_sleep"></string>
        <string name="english"></string>
        <string name="spanish"></string>

        <string name="pc_setup_title"></string>
        <string name="name_field"></string>
        <string name="pronouns_field"></string>
        <string name="language_field"></string>
        <string name="she_her"></string>
        <string name="he_his"></string>
        <string name="they_them"></string>
        <string name="first_name"></string>
        <string name="choose_one"></string>
        <string name="welcome_title"></string>
        <string name="welcome_text"></string>

        <string name="home"></string>
        <string name="community_center"></string>
        <string name="health_clinic"></string>
        <string name="library"></string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_1_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_1_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_2_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_2_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_3_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_3_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_4_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_rashad_4_desc"></string>
    
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_1_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_1_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_2_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_2_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_3_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_3_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_4_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lila_4_desc"></string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_1_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_1_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_2_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_2_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_3_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_3_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_4_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_calindas_4_desc"></string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_1_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_1_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_2_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_2_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_3_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_3_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_4_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_lee_4_desc"></string>

        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_1_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_1_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_2_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_2_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_3_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_3_desc"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_4_title"></string>
        <string name="end_of_quest_elisa_4_desc"></string>

        <string name="tutorial_building"></string>
        <string name="tutorial_phone"></string>
        <string name="tutorial_todo"></string>
        <string name="tutorial_notes"></string>
        <string name="tutorial_contacts"></string>

        <string name="meet"></string>
        <string name="good_morning_message"></string>
        
    </Spanish>

</languages>